Some mysteries are beyond belief.
True Story is a crime, drama, history film directed by Rupert Goold.
A drama centered on the relationship between journalist Michael Finkel and Christian
Longo, an FBI Most Wanted List murderer who for years lived outside the U.S.
under Finkel's name.
Michael Finkel, played by Jonah Hill.
Christian Longo, played by James Franco.
Jill Barker, played by Felicity Jones.
Mary Jane Longo, played by Maria Dizzia.
Pat Frato, played by Ethan Suplee.
Greg Ganley, played by Robert John Burke.
True Story is a 2015 American mystery thriller film that was
directed by Rupert Goold in his directorial debut.
It is based on a screenplay by Goold and David Kajganich.
Based on the memoir of the same name by Michael Finkel, it stars Jonah Hill, James Franco and
Felicity Jones, with Gretchen Mol, Betty Gilpin and John Sharian in supporting roles.
Franco plays Christian Longo, a man on the Federal Bureau of Investigation's
most-wanted list accused of murdering his wife and three children in Oregon.
He hid in Mexico using the identity of Michael
Finkel, a journalist played by Hill.
The film premiered at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival and was released
theatrically on April 17, 2015, in the United States.
It explores the relationship that develops between the two men after
journalist Finkel begins to meet with Longo in prison.
The film explores themes of prison, journalist,
prisoner, based on true story, prison visit.
The tone is emotional.